

CONTACT ME

070-9034-4134

sunnyliumifune@gmail.com

https://github.com/SunnyMifune

m www.linkedin.com/in/sunnymifune

EDUCATION

Web Development Le Wagon Tokyo 2022.10-2022.12

Business Administration Dept.
Soochow University/Master degree
2017-2018

Business Administration Dept.
Soochow University/Bachelor degree
2013-2017

SKILLS

Frontend

HTML, CSS, JavaScript ES6, Bootstrap, React

Backend

Ruby on Rails, Python

Design

Figma, Illustrator, Photoshop

LANGUAGES

Mandarin: native

English: fluent

Japanese: conversational

Sunny Mifune

Frontend Engineer

ABOUT ME

I was born and grew up in Taiwan. I love classical music and began violin study since 6 years old. Also, I have joined the Taipei civic symphony orchestra for 9 years since my freshman year in college.

I really enjoy designing the page, making the page from 0 to functional brings me a sense of accomplishment, and that's why I am really interested in frontend work.

WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

Freshout (Team role: front-end + back-end)

http://www.freshout.world/

The app can easily show what food the user has in their fridge, and the app also can inform users of the expiration date to prevent the waste of food.

// Ruby on Rails, HTML, CSS, Javascript, API

Farm-bnb (Team role: front-end)

https://farm-bnb.herokuapp.com/

Users can book the animals on the website when they need help from animals working for their farm.

// Ruby on Rails, HTML, CSS, Javascript, API

WORK EXPERIENCE

Merchandiser (Pre-order Dept.)

2021.09-2022.09

Li & Fung Limited I Taipei, Taiwan

- Communicate and follow up with internal and external constituents, including clients, vendors, mills, and colleagues, to solve problems as soon as possible.
- Build and maintain close relationships with buyers in order to understand their goals and provide them with suitable sourcing services.

Logistic Assistant

2021.04-2021.09

KindMinds Innovations I Taipei, Taiwan

- Create sea or express shipment to send products oversea.
- Tracking packages if arrive on time and calculating the accounts receivable.
- Weekly checking the Amazon FBA system, sometime the system will have an

Assistant Merchandiser (Production Dept.)

2018.10-2020-06

Li & Fung Limited I Taipei, Taiwan

- Manage production for the children's accessories / active apparel industry, like monitoring the transit calendars, orders, production progress, and shipping to ensure deliveries.
- System information update.